<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SilentWhisper</string>
    <string name="TandC">1. Introduction\n Welcome to [App Name], an anonymous messaging service that allows users to communicate without revealing their identities. By using this app, you agree to be bound by these terms and conditions, and you consent to the collection, use, and sharing of your data as described in our Privacy Policy.\n\n 2. Eligibility\n You must be at least 13 years old to use the app. By using this app, you represent that you meet the minimum age requirement and are legally permitted to use this service.\n\n 3. Account Creation and Anonymity\n\n The app does not require users to create identifiable accounts (no names, email addresses, or phone numbers are required). Communication is facilitated through anonymous identifiers assigned to each user.\n 4. User Responsibilities\n - Respectful Use: Users must use the app in a manner that is respectful of others. Hate speech, harassment, abusive language, or any form of bullying will not be tolerated.\n - Legal Compliance: Users are responsible for ensuring that their use of the app complies with all applicable laws and regulations. Illegal activities such as threats, cyberbullying, impersonation, and unauthorized distribution of content are strictly prohibited.\n - No Sharing of Personal Information: Users are prohibited from sharing personal information (yours or others) through the app.\n - User-Generated Content: All messages sent via the app are the responsibility of the user who sends them. The app is not liable for any user-generated content that is illegal, offensive, or violates others\' rights.\n 5. Privacy and Data Collection\n The app prioritizes user privacy and collects minimal data. The following types of data may be collected:\n - Device Information: We may collect device information for security and troubleshooting purposes.\n - Message Metadata: Metadata related to messages (e.g., time sent) may be collected but not the message content itself.\n - Location Data: If you opt-in, location data may be collected for specific features such as location-based chat rooms.\n 6. Data Retention\n Messages are not permanently stored on our servers. Once delivered to the recipient(s), the message is deleted from our servers.\n 7. Limitation of Liability\n The app is provided on an basis without any warranties. We are not liable for any damages arising from the use or misuse of the app.</string>
</resources>